
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is crypto currency?",
    answer: "Digital currency",
    options: [
      "Digital currency",
      "Gold currency",
      "AR currency ",
      "Wire transfer"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "When was first decentralised cryptocurrency created?",
    answer: "2009",
    options: [
      "2007",
      "2011",
      "2009",
      "2010"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which was the First decentralised crypto currency?",
    answer: "Bitcoin",
    options: [
      "Litecoin",
      "Bitcoin",
      "Dogecoin",
      "Yearn finance"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which Pseudo-anonymous developer created Bitcoin? ",
    answer: "Satoshi Nakamoto",
    options: [
      "Vitalik buterin",
      "Elon Musk",
      "Satoshi Nakamoto",
      "Billy Markus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which was the first country to accept Bitcoin legally?",
    answer: "El Salvador",
    options: [
      "El Salvador",
      "USA",
      "India",
      "Japan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How does crypto currency runs?",
    answer: "Blockchain",
    options: [
      "Web",
      "Blockchain",
      "Chainlink",
      "Optical Fibre"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many type of crypto currency(tokens) are there?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "3",
      "8",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Most common or used tokens are?",
    answer: "Both A and B",
    options: [
      "Utility",
      "Payment",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What are digital pictures or fungible tokens called?",
    answer: "NFTs",
    options: [
      "GIFs",
      "Stickers",
      "NFTs",
      "PNG"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who was the first person to introduce Crypto ATMs?",
    answer: "Jordan Kelley",
    options: [
      "Jordan Kelley",
      "Vitalik Buterin",
      "Satoshi Nakamoto",
      "Elon Musk"
    ]
  },

];